http://www.rallyschool.com.au/privacy-policy

This website uses the cookies & tracking technologies outlined below. To learn more about cookies & how to control/delete cookies, see this article by Choice magazine, Australia’s leading independent consumer advocacy group. To learn more about local storage, see this article.
To clear all tracking stored in your browser (including cookies and local storage) for this domain, CLICK HERE.
The policy below corresponds to the cookies & tracking on this website only. This website may integrate with external provider(s) for some of its functionality (eg. payment gateways, booking engines). While we have engaged in all reasonable efforts to ensure that these providers’ cookies & tracking operations are as close to our own policy as possible, your usage of these providers is subject to each provider’s own privacy and/or cookies policy.
Necessary Cookies
These cookies are necessary for our website to function and as such are automatically installed. For example:
Helping route the website to your browser efficiently using our IT infrastructure.
Saving your data on multi-page forms/checkouts (of any).
Letting you share or like our content on social networks like Facebook and Twitter if the relevant widgets are present on our pages. If you are logged into a social network, these widgets will automatically let you share content to your account if you choose.
Preference Cookies
These cookies save your preferences for any customisation of the website (eg. your closest track location) and are installed if you make a customisation.
Statistical Cookies & Tracking
These cookies help us determine user behaviour on the website by reporting on your session. These technologies do not cross-reference your browsing with data from other websites. If you are located in the European Economic Area, we ask each tool to only use a session cookie (ie. one that instructs the browser to clear it once you’ve finished your session).
Technologies used:
Google Analytics (Privacy Policy | Opt Out) for tracking general & custom behaviour on the website. We use all options that Google Analytics provides for maximising your privacy including instructing it to anonymise your IP address, transmitting data by an SSL connection only and manually stripping out any personally identifiable information before transmitting to Google Analytics.
Third Party Tracking/Marketing Cookies
These cookies cross-reference your browsing with data from other websites to provide us with more accurate aggregated reports and to enable us to serve you personalised ads, including ads based on your browsing behaviour on this website. This functionality is aggregated: we do not use any provider that allows us to see your specific data or to create an ad specifically for you. If you are located in the European Economic Area, we do not use these cookies.
Technologies used:
Google Analytics Doubleclick (Privacy Policy | Opt Out) for providing us aggregated reporting of your demographics & interests as determined by Google from any Google accounts you have, as well as allowing us to serve you ads on third party websites based on your browsing behaviour. If you opt into data sharing with Google, your visits to the website across different devices where you’re logged into Google will be tied together in a set of aggregated, anonymised usage reports. Google does not show us this data on an individual basis.
Google Ads (Privacy Policy | Opt Out) as above but this also allows Google to deduplicate your browsing sessions to this website across multiple browsers/devices for the purposes of tracking conversions.
Facebook Ads (Privacy Policy | Opt Out) allows us to serve you ads based on your browsing behaviour on our website as well as see aggregate reports that deduplicate your browsing sessions to this website across multiple browsers/devices.
A/B Testing & Personalisation Cookies
These cookies allow us to improve our website by consistently showing you the same variation of a website and seeing which variation engages users more. This functionality is aggregated: we do not use any provider that allows us to see your specific data or to create an ad specifically for you. If you are located in the European Economic Area, we do not use these cookies.
Technologies used:
Google Optimize (Privacy Policy | Opt Out) for serving different versions of one or more pages on our website based on a combination of chance and selected targeting criteria (eg. your location or referral source).
CRM and CRM-Like Cookies/Tracking
These cookies allow us to view some aspects of your website browsing behaviour on an individual basis. No providers we use store any personally identifiable data in the cookie, what’s stored instead is a pseudonymous identifier (eg. your account ID) which is then tied to any additional data on the provider’s end (ie. not in your browser or on the website). If you are located in the European Economic Area, we do not use these cookies.
Technologies used:
Google Analytics UserID (Privacy Policy | Opt Out) for combining the standard Google Analytics reports with a pseudonymous and/or encrypted identifier. This occurs only if you choose to personally identify yourself on this website (eg. by creating an account or entering your details into a form.
Contact Us
LocationNSW: Sydney (Colo Heights)NSW: Newcastle/HunterSA: Adelaide (Barossa)QLD: Brisbane (Ipswich)VIC: Melbourne (Werribee)WA: Perth (Bakers Hill)Unsure?
COVID-19: Keep me updated with new dates and important information.
Copyright 2018 Rally School Australia | All Rights Reserved |
(Colo Park)
Hunter Valley
(Hunter Valley)
Brisbane
(Willowbank)
Adelaide
(Truro)
Melbourne
(Mount Cottrell)
Perth
(Bakers Hill)
Sydney
(Colo Park)
Hunter Valley
(Hunter Valley)
Brisbane
(Willowbank)
Adelaide
(Truro)
Melbourne
(Mount Cottrell)
Perth
(Bakers Hill)
Sydney
(Colo Park)
Hunter Valley
(Hunter Valley)
Brisbane
(Willowbank)
Adelaide
(Truro)
Melbourne
(Mount Cottrell)
Perth
(Bakers Hill)
Sydney
(Colo Park)
Hunter Valley
(Hunter Valley)
Brisbane
(Willowbank)
Adelaide
(Truro)
Melbourne
(Mount Cottrell)
Perth
(Bakers Hill)
Sydney
(Colo Park)
Hunter Valley
(Hunter Valley)
Brisbane
(Willowbank)
Adelaide
(Truro)
Melbourne
(Mount Cottrell)
Perth
(Bakers Hill)
